hi welcome back to the online we treat
the wheel of life retreat Jintao shaman
will have a quarter to three months a
new home and I'd like to thank Allison
for coming in translating but won't come
on a listen but addenda you have ended
our session 16 is called a life to live
don't hang up on without a llama cook no
relation
and now you see this group of people but
y'all got bang bang young and I just
walking down the street with my books
under and each one is walking through
the wheel of life by my own bunch a new
home and pretty much there in only two
of the links we cover a whole human but
how new ji Hye Jung choking and getting
caught about gum come on kid marry those
two links if just before them comes link
number 10
hanging ding dong a joke hey too many
unusual movie and you can see it here
well combine or die this is my kids
painters kid painters from Nepal a new
Han Xin Yi Lin Tony pann cotton and they
have said that this lady is supposed to
be a pregnant lady but do not hang up
all night you knew them of knowing when
time and she represents link number 10
super super super super but quite a yang
Qian Yin Yin Xiu me to pass cheaper to
what she means number 10 - Ella
so my super is a difficult word it has
been mistranslated many times she bought
a motor car but uh will you sign you
long
it can mean possible Patel I got a it
can mean becoming not gonna yell at
Charton
it can mean your whole life I cook I
cook man it doesn't mean any of those
here but cooking here now Chennai and I
think it was a big breakthrough my own
teacher taught me don't know funky taiko
told I told you sir in this case you
have to think of the word sipper means
karma which is ripe
oh my denied don't young hot Nikon fine
need anti-cheat balcony like Nichkhun so
back in link number 2 white line in
being so high we had karma which was
like a seed that you just put under the
ground dude I couldn't get my young man
young man give my dog a product and we
translated that is fresh company but the
chicken is fresh karma but I'm tired I
get nah I need my towel Pachi Pachi line
and get my towel and you know remember
we put the seed under the ground banging
and yelling tell you not in the spring
vamoose on watermelon seed kill you home
and then it rained was out all Qaeda
move and the water touch the scene when
the camera had young and it woke up all
the workers in the factory inside the
seed young young young my bench opium
I pictured them they are like you know
doomed I knew hung up or dentist gave
the supervisor racer What's Wrong yeah
everybody what you do and I young me
file on we gotta get ready to push this
sprout out of this city name
and so during those few months time
while we take them to play young
right-hander after the water touches the
seed cioppino jump ahead young i don't
know strange things are happening inside
of the scene new new killer I mean John
Young we finished those two preparation
preparing the factory to open don't
gotta hang duck - Juba dollar should you
wait on your mind mugger they were
called gay Pacific Cooper limber link
number eight and called a sheep re / -
Paula Bunyan decontamination we took the
good seats - Bellamy young top and did
coffee meditation I'm happy but I think
of phyto handful to the jib either
and on top of that we did a high-powered
understanding about this which makes
good seeds open faster and bigger but in
hello to dioxin he'll be so suffering
young I'm joining top nine Yin hung but
all on her
with necrosis when you have young to
cook in the picture of The Wheel of Life
kombucha new bunch and boy link number
18 in soup antigen we did sort of a
negative coffee meditation don't our
data came about think of Ithaca we were
like I'm glad I'm eating me I will get
stronger cantata yum you all to man with
oriented Toshi equipment huh and then
more more terrible
what sort of time T canto time we think
there's no such thing as Karma the pain
comes from deep in Canadian company
opening to fake a book
even if I kill an animal to eat a
cannoli makan my aunt at night I
don't believe anything will happen to me
to contention about cooking you say then
went on so because of those two ideas
well they have eaten August bad sees in
the Wheel of Life get stronger and
stronger when you had young shouting
much Aloha you can make it link number 2
well I mean so much go to the book let's
go to the text Andy Jenkins attended end
on one man it says to Parsippany what is
link number 10 which is called ripe
karma in Somali geek a year ago language
in Narducci Keane I'm Shelley keep
Archer girl earlier in the wheel do not
know much Aloha on the second link which
is called DJ and Tibetan and sanskara in
Sanskrit linking so had a goal to pay
anything but samskaara counting Fang
remember link number 1 was you know you
walk into the kitchen and your husband
yells at you
initially when will talk to me a bit I'm
a good man you see I didn't Iike to
commit as an element as like link number
1 which is misunderstanding where he's
coming from
what a new kingship my blood in LA he
was having an identity that
misunderstanding pushes link number 2
so you shy daughter I didn't do so Hank
and she makes cover but why tongue it
how monk now I'm not stupid you're
stupid to her husband who I know become
income you know and mine you know
so the DJ in the text here the sanskara
is the moment that she says I'm not
stupidest but they do change on Roman
when I - I'm irrelevant when I am coming
up and my noona and then the guard shack
which means a seed pod about nila yung
guna of the karma is pressed under mind
look unwelcome tea
okay my dog is not only blind and Darrin
topical come on buddy
now sometimes he pooper in the house by
accident
well yeah I'm tryna combo that HM yeah
then sometimes on the carpet then paint
and hum and you know we try to lift up
our very carefully go young wife on the
on one gave a a little bit of
smell will rub into the carpet welcome
to Moshe Tom about pom pom so the verb
here girl girl girl means that smell
gets rubbed into the carpet in this case
the Carl are saying I'm not stupid
you're stupid
don't kill hop now you go big boy I'm
coming up and my mom gets rubbed into
our mind in yo Tom Tom J equal to that
and this is gonna be important later but
weakness again and hey John Sean I we've
been talking about the third language
system one of the monkeys you know the
English uh bottom of German concrete and
that monkey represents your mind
entering your mother's womb welcome to
cook at mind and leave out to come to
may get mad but when it can also
represent the carpet carpet where the
stinky is you know computed idea tom tom
tom tom tom tom so at the moment that
the wife says I'm not stupid you're
stupid provide equipment move on or I'm
coming up and mine had cameras rubbed
into them mindstream neat Dobby in yo
John Young taunted
and that's another meaning of the
thirdly what anima being a cackling
Indian Shobha so the third leg first we
understand it as the mind coming into my
mother's womb when you news about angel
tae-hyun on unit I'm talking about don't
go Google me but we can also understand
the third link as the mind in which the
seed is pressed when she said I'm not
stupid
you don't come but Aisha pioneer at my
choked on it Yahweh in yo Wow big way
and coming up and Manuel
then at that moment when the seat is
pressed into the mind I'm not stupid
okay
young me in your watch on time took em
coming up and waking up
it's like the watermelon seed was just
put under the dirt well you know my
daughter
then what's the water was the fertilizer
we finished it in the last class so
don't look like a fumble you do not have
some do not compute
in the last class we finished with the
water and what's the fertilizer children
absolutely - Bangi and remember it was
like with a bad seed it's two different
things when you're down here I'm so
behind you know it's like she told her
friend my husband let me go I know the
new bank elemento new toad and I her
friend sorry
come come to buoy and I shouldn't angry
mouth it's like she's doing a negative
coffee meditation well you go ahead and
think of a to cook and she has no idea
that her kids are gonna be bad for many
weeks because of what she said to her
husband welcome Bianca Congo koishi-chan
and who home - mutant over in India
going over job so that that's it's
sailing key set up the bad seed now has
been given water and fertilizer by her
negative coffee meditation and by young
so but yeah bye I think afraid to cook
cook away but I show you shine no I got
seed from link number 2 which is I
didn't I'm not stupid you're stupid
well you had you're not hanging so hang
on I'm coming up and man you know it
becomes to change the song now get on
teaching the song to change the song to
sing the song to song to show her the
seed becomes - 2 mins tremendous power
young gotten to talking in a tsukemen
bottle like nuclear power me no no no
then what power does it have now after
her negative coffee meditation but not
also we think effective cocoa a lady
she may loop him now that's it can shoot
a new lifetime can project a new
lifetime she men you tell me you have
young knucklehead our demo keeps on my
computer I'm against the meaning of
super super link number 10 why not a
super chilling new someone it's
represented by a pregnant woman Maggie
my morning man time but that woman's big
belly represents a big income or pack
your lungs and sound a louder
then the seeds let's open the sprout
comes up so happy I'm not a commuter and
we see the picture here of a birth 3 of
a child being born but I would Janet I
come up with Chad and Lucinda
I think a lot about these images like an
arrow in the eye to need a new vision
and an animal would Angela
or a baby coming out of a woman heimo
blue barracks in down 104
in these ancient paintings don't mean
lookin Conan
this must have been very very shocking
new dealership like they didn't have
videos home call video but I think if if
Buddha had a computer and video
oh god video Antonio to up okay
making a video he would have made a
movie about this wheel of life and not
not paintings missile a mobile fame
weapon say look how I name a company you
can bear and I think someday would be
interesting to make a real evocative
movie like big emotions now Donna such a
young girl I'm with him your inner tube
serving you well Fintan camel oh come on
big guy
where somebody has an arrow in their eye
in the exact I online I try to find
someone who got shot with the air and it
did happen once and the person went to
the hospital
welcome attention McArthur crowd to the
Kogan team kim jimin's and quiet don't
be a long one without a vowel being
but these pictures are are supposed to
like frickin mutiny you new long to
dementia come on you see this picture
baby coming out of a woman and the
women's bodies being torn apart cable
finessing congregate I go hopefully then
we Sarah
then we're supposed to think you know I
don't want to do that again so don't you
tell you knew me lad look I'm doing a
long know what you don't want to do
again you don't want to be the woman oh
you don't want to be the baby I'm gonna
do better I don't want to be either way
look how much other noon Oh God okay -
typical means no the deceit is cracking
open to cheat my keep on your line the
fat suit and your map and child is
coming up text says that I set up a now
that the seed was given its water and
it's fertilizer by the negative no one
may know take think effective Yangtze
Jubilees Nippert agenda so attend attend
their based on that karma now being
totally ripe well yeah you can Whitney
torment in huntin cane a supercar into
Tom Burlinson in some jar then the mind
cook makes the crossing so not I'm to
tau mobile wah into one of the four
kinds of birth
well jumbo risin
and that the moment after the crossing
welcome quack social bond why we call
rebirth kumbaya
I said link number 11 in doing so my mom
you could say birth you could say
rebirth occupation Oh guess not the
first the first time it happened it
wasn't a rebirth right
Tyson is no first term come : no Dean we
have been here countless times there's
no beginning they wouldn't get bushes
but now the first time I heard that it
was very uncomfortable for me
no no thing to me a new dollar income
tato a mile um we'd like to think that
there was a big bang God made the world
hotline you think it makes us feel
comfortable if we think there was a
beginning you know commercial but now
but it's not logical you not come up
late nothing can start unless somebody
else something else moves before that
come got about no joke a code to get a
kingdom to talk so you could really
translate this link number eleven you
could always translate it as rebirth we
might get by they took show you an
Indian women like a bank along it
knowing you laugh I said the textures
into one of the four kinds of birth we
are done by no idea optimum relation and
this is a popular topic in the ancient
determine text but I'll a mob to
therefore being don't you bang-bang
convey you far
and because we don't know what's the
four kinds of birth commit boom racing
and he doesn't mention them in the text
but I hummed I kept on bang bang I
thought we should go to another book and
and get a nice commentary on this fourth
down and about cool shot captain Bammer
pan - yeah hey Bob Russian da so we're
gonna follow the Tibetan here to the
commentary the vitamin D tell mangu yeah
I think that I can a La Nina now you can
divide all the kinds of birth into four
man kata tête-à-tête motion and boom boy
and I remember this was the first book I
ever studied with my teacher what we
know today like without into the tunnel
title we started 45 years ago you
thought about now boom Balaam Namjoo it
took us 12 years to finish this book
well don't mock my hand I'm different or
not so keen a was always a confusing
word for me my king national lunatic oh
hey over time k means born kg Lucinda
name is location Nashville Nina did him
and then you know after many years you
learn to translate it more correctly
it's not location of birth it's the type
of so you know my my tongue in golden
solid idioms in Darren Ola that's in DES
so here's the name of the for provide a
lot I go boom rushing me okay gone kids
a good to shake a tushy
so the first one is called me okay help
indigo Nanyang cake no means a room like
human mothers young vanilla multi I mean
to come come on me man KS the past tense
of born so burned in the past in the
womb born in the world
now you're gonna what cushioned every
Rhino loosen that up the compact okay
go which is sometimes split into Ghana
means egg okay going on here Tintin
kirtan Gong in yell at you so some
beings are born from egg something
are born from wounds immobilization
Lucinda - - mom was a something gotta -
don't by the way in Buddhism young they
may come down further the real birth is
at the moment of conception she talks a
lot I concur to time then there's a
second birth out of the room or out of
the so don't walk so she until hanging
why to come watching
but it's the conception which is when
the baby starts new knowledge Alto time
allocated yeah but now there's a living
sentient being at the moment of
conception
boom boom shown back on cocteau time the
third one is called Suki sheesh anybody
got a suitcase sometimes it's called the
Kiowas it Akira super cool super it
means miraculous / no Cannella she
shouldn't get you question for example
the Christians believe that Jesus was
born without a father without sex will
not help out until been done to you so
Lucinda so much I come over hey Tanya
and Hindus believe that the great yoga
master Patanjali 100 didn't booked a
yoga pant le he was born in the holy
water he appeared in the holy water that
his mother offered to King John my
Manion that water offering with your
hands is called anjali young tango don't
I go get my ruler and chili pot means
further by party nila - Oh sir his name
his whole life he was called the guy who
fell down from the sky into the water
but actually then those people are born
complete so then in your native syndrome
wanting them to share to share lockira
so - chair like you that means in the
summer time not only la mujer when the
weather is warm and there's lots of rain
puddles on the ground create I think I'm
like on you will not merchants
the ancient people they couldn't see the
eggs of the insects negotiate how come
ten now taking gocarygo me job so they
called it a birth from warmth and
moisture with a hollow joomla solution
to show option so there's the four kinds
of birth like abomination birth from the
womb shouldn't old high birth from egg
Shindo June miracle birth cinta shall
kill you
and birth from warmth and moisture well
shouldn't the hi I'm Lambie now just for
fun I thought you guys would like to
continue reading this text but yeah you
vote on it when we get my update 1 by 9
which is related to the text being
translated by our translator C Gong XI
from Singapore only went above an
identikit budget you shouldn't read into
Singapore
same mother Kouga from about 500 years
ago I am damn good okay so I thought
you'd like to hear some discussion about
this for Hillgrove if I don't get my cat
meow long way bum rush at night he died
like me okay can you take hungry ghosts
also have birth from a room it's
possible they are not just miracle
usually we think they just born suddenly
ya Hungry Ghost but he says they can
also be born from a room so also is a
imply usually they are born in another
way but they also have oh not about
hiding or computer Shinda to show King
looks enjoy what I accomplished in doubt
about how awake come to me no wait and
about Julie there's an other done and
they say these are called stories of
spiritual people reunited the whole line
encoding Google amulet from ancient
India okay I'm Loco and this one is
called the story of the lady Hungry
Ghost
well King neither coaching good no we
don't and there's a famous verse that
she used to recite mono team
acquaintance um darkening babka someone
young need not get a second dollar
symbol may I give birth from right to
500 kids everyday tonight I said there
are number yet about high five hundred
hungry ghosts kids come out of my room
every day every day someday we'd ocean
try to complete her name Robin a some
more young up yet a and at night in the
dark I have another 500
yeah from home come on Tyson random
tempting weekend then you you might
think you know how does Hungry Ghost mom
take care of her 1000 per day Hungry
Ghost kiss want to come back away I am
so we don't make up camo paint it we
don't morning circle I eat them
searching time to toilet Simba mere but
still I don't feel for you on come come
they know okay Jason future Milani
Ganesha guy you take all four kinds of
birth are found with human beings the
compilation doodle team time I say
something they have all four guys got
the car boom right on this is very
standard and famous abhidharma
discussion what illiyyun think i'ma go
tell Louie you Fatoumata noting me
personnel make a most humans as we know
are born from the womb Oh headlong
YouTube debate ocean got about high
summer UK some are born miraculously so
what you came up solución de mostest as
porn complete because they just born as
a complete dune eyelash in the hunt in
mop a whole ocean Rankin and they give
the example of the Buddhist master named
aryadeva
famous disciple of Nagarjuna do that we
overbooked I for captain Llyod Ava they
don't know thinking I'll go China
I don't know the story we can look at us
someday but he apparently he was born
miraculously to Cochin I do packet I
teamed up normal plain old onion in you
know my looks and gamma continue then a
couple - okay tower to Sheila Kay then
there was a king who was born from the
top of the head of his father from
warmth and moisture no komova pollution
rather didn't how good I am
I told her I'm bad
then there are two are hurts to people
who became a highway and I Hangul
toolbar in Tibetan they're called shark
and in return something I think all that
chocolate and they were born from egg
production due to
turned Ola young she hired animals also
have four kinds of birth offer Google
Russian the também like yad aksaram part
o Lord Zhu Qiqi chapter but all hell
beings all Devas and all part of beings
are born completely helpings Devas and
part of the cartoon sending to taken to
me Lucinda went and always born
miraculously to San Diego to thing madam
- mum halle-loo syndrome tu
he'll be Devin and part of something
updating button to one
yeah so part of being it members that
one in the moment after you die and you
go into the bottle don't you want a
vineyard or a tongue job on that one
shall pick up and get back up
anybody my age or then we'll meet your
name
Danny cause I'll be damned kosher which
is the most famous book of our Biederman
nowadays well I did you come cool ante
that Marco saloon on a couch that no t
need to be you know uh namdong
hannam-dong super primer to take a all
helpings all diverse and all part of
beings are born complete miraculously
the car to San Diego to team returned to
mum you loosen grant it won't cut K you
which brings us to link number 12
you know don't add onion being show me
hang the last of the twelve links yongi
in cocoon time we hanging and the
picture you see is there somebody
carrying a big package on their bed
junkman gentile i'm going up north and
we're mobile Oh totally and this this
represents the way that people were
buried or how they treated dead bodies
in ancient India and also in Tibet don't
you come caca policy Lake accepted oh no
God I come here at a time
then there's some kind of if you think
your job is bad at least you are not
carrying corpses to the mountain or to
the we call the burial we call the
Charnel ground shuttle ground means a
very terrible place where you throw dead
body so you just throw them on the girl
oh come on Deacon wake up man that is
knit a pinecone five that means a
challenge and aloha don't you know once
I know one secondly I'm of my to
complete my whole name insecure cap and
a name how soon
I'll tell you a story Yoshi can I talk
about you I was a young mom I was living
in a monster but wasn't a monkey TomTom
tubing you thought you file a motion she
small Mongolian monastery in America's
not moving mom calling army and the
senior teacher of the time of love the
yummy coconut back LACMA
he was very famous for one day I have to
drive him in the car so I'm showing you
my office this is Mike I mean oli Mike
he says Oh Mike is very good oh my oh my
look ya'll go away he'll be you
then the monetary loss sir the kinase he
quote the first line of the second
chapter may I touch it
young young loading couch into her and I
was memorized
the avatar Micajah at that time I never
finished by finished three or four
chapters book a day that might go solo -
chobe etiquette and biofuels just
finished the game now hang on big neo
that's the first line at the second
chapter I explained hmm
Oh which is behind I but you said no
Mike unions very dry for some time and
the two big llamas in the back they fell
asleep I read that my official diorama
to start to talk to me well we're taking
we had a wonderful talk for like two
hours but I don't tell me everything on
time Oh companion tell me what your last
cemetery imploding in one okay okay
many crosses but yeah oh what's that
many crosses don't like it I show you do
to deter what I do not own any change
this is why they have those crosses on
yellow - aha conn-young caitanya know I
said well they buried the body
dohno job yet I don't
what though the whole body de combo time
check not the ashes
welcome pie choco no no they believe
that the body the person will come alive
at the end of the world they will go to
hell calm calm hotend uncle Tariq will
also some live I looked and I maja said
d13 do
then he look at me haha oh yeah and over
good huh huh what a waste of good living
space people can live on that land right
why they put the dead body so we can
monetize all right yo mo chedda you
don't like what should we do
brother Harvey - done LMB ever said yet
then it's what you see in this picture
but i do kappa eh ah moochin like we cut
the party we cut all the pieces of
chakra to me
we mix it with some flour with flour
Toto john-boy Pablo my probably and we
carry it to the top of the mountain but
no man landed knowing and we give it to
the birds
but employ Canyon konkey my and then
it's a good color well known among the
top that person's body is not wasted
that person's body is a gift to to this
wild animals sake double-entry check it
on a map one quarter when you don't open
yeah so that's what's happening here
later on you yeah you know they come
with a nice picture
10:18 yep Akashi cheering button there
MK drop again then we come to the last
link which is link number 12 tip agent
aha playing Indian cooking game show me
how she got she means AG and because she
got she gonna like it yeah but yet and
technically it's called
death maybe with aging the Mackey talk
nadu Cola Ketchikan any convey - yeah
gosh she's cheating for tender means
yeah
then I I asked my teacher why they call
it death with maybe some aging but I got
old I sound like a chuckle anyway - yeah
then my teacher said well sometimes kids
die in the womb but I go tonight eight
okay DJ get your mouth I don't know when
I do become B okay so that's a that's
why Buddha didn't make thirteen volatile
compound we're binding do some some
people die in the womb so much about hi
they don't have time together yeah
they're goin a pumpernickel English
ending member in what is the definition
of aging let me echo yaaayyy
the body goes to change change change
change it never stays the same
good AJ what I don't I don't I don't I
don't know combo you're Ewing
it falls apart step by step well I'm
walking with mom
day by day no one named ok now the
definition of death
yeah danique ok check she will need
complete interim chief policy when we
say death what we mean is that the flow
of the same body in mind is interrupted
Cubano de cachoeira moon omj kokumo
khatai patented billion by
so we don't say the body died or the
mine stopped if I don't I'll come not
gotten that jet hey I'm talking it takes
on a different clothing blenman
whoa whoa okay so it's very interesting
that death is it's not the end of the
party or domaine we're I not a to Bray
let it come find a circuit to Phuket I
hate them too
the mind shifts I'm touching knowing the
physical form shifts and yang Wei Chen
died but life does not end and cannot
end Newsome come you're alive I can take
that hope you have lived for a time with
no beginning and you will live for time
with no end
don't bother some new Keep Calm cause I
Delta J tip-top some were competitive
I'd like to end this session with kind
of a review the moon gate open and I
hope that I'm gonna be using special
images but oh sure you mean that me
we've had all twelve links no way I
don't add up on all my hanging you and
I've taught them in groups in different
days
what I ate Hampton um I mean I know
and I'd like to just review that because
it's gonna be important tomorrow and the
next day's why don't you move on Populi
but wait don't say wench I'm talking in
mind when your name detail so in this
first picture here you see of the twelve
links and then I said this morning I
learned how to write a MOOC and OT
opinion time with hanging game was so
long why chosen I how cutting out it's
like it was done by a kid but it's done
by me the way
Nonya you do family Canyon first I want
to draw your attention that the first
two links hang together
no mundo hoops at U equal the bandwidth
hanging doubting you can catch on your
hand you can call it missin you could
call it ignorance and caramel mocha but
I go and all I shall come here weeping
but I'd like to call it understanding
and I want you to think of these two
together
you go into lambda y de la mente
completo then misunderstanding triggers
secondly Russia you should I could try
being so high then she says I'm we're
going on in coming up and one of those
two things kind of hang together
why hanging getting I can get thing out
okay now the next image
you can't depends are poorly written
yellow cloud come open none not mine my
window ran with my around legs three up
to seven kwan-yuen doing tabata bite and
these are the five links which are kind
of our equipment during life
they're what we use to express ourselves
well I mean Union England second codon
supa dupa dupa she um tonight I hang
Bank hung in the third link we get a
mind doing so but in the fourth link we
start to get a body along with that mind
insider mom coming gene so bummed about
now hunk over time pub in Jamaica Japan
in the fifth link our eyes ears nose
they start to we start to get our
equipment for for contacting the outside
I'm getting shown a month time we don't
I don't about mauka take way they don't
act like a year but while six things we
use those instruments to make contact
with the etc Dominion shows how to
Terrace a youngin take banana to attack
with the urban wine
and then in the seventh thing we started
feeling about what we contacted but I'll
jump in you buy don't about our I'm
going cool - tada - attack so you can
kind of get a feeling that links three
tilling seven they kind of hang together
there are the equipment that we need to
be alive when I could buy a goat I come
up like a young Canadian show battleship
identify now to magnetic baby but you
back on station in the next image then
we can tip hell I drew yellow cloud
around eight nine and ten then we can
tip pal to the hem up not my Moran so
one can you pump didn't move and really
when you think about it
the most important version of eight nine
and ten is at the end of our life but I
look like a man even in our mind from
her whole life including I'm not stupid
come to my room and coming up and my
moon up and then we talked about how
it's very important which seed is
activated in the last moment of our
conscious life so now you better know
that I'm going on with it now
who the hell now she looked at my father
cuckoo cuckoo some call it a Koopa so as
you see in the image here links eight
and nine and we writing in Canada Indian
show pumpkin is that big fat seed that
already got a lot of water and
fertilizer but unusual move up map back
are look new new parfum bong into now
and then eight or nine or like the water
and fertilizer on that see but are you
doing time by didn't am nilüfer Fung
Wong let him wrong
then if you think about it department
even our link number eleven and Link
number 12
ringing Shaboom opening shoe behind
rebirth aging
day by day after you conceived and then
there I said yeah being a one isolated
bangle Totoro jetties
just eleven and twelve is a whole life
term dementia women when we had a talk
about 9/11 is is coming into the would
mean trouble him up then leave about
time but we already came into the room
in number three you don't already felt
about item Indian shoe bar so I want you
to start to get this feeling
don't look at my work I'm shop nine this
is not one life from beginning to end
like Shakespeare sperm and icon file I'm
honored to look but now I look at
talking to my otaku Shakespeare
something else is going on here yay all
right 11 and 12 are a whole lot
themselves you show me more Tommy
highlight a code-nine coaching jump I
wanted to kind of sound like they happen
before your mind came into this one mom
well hi I'm Tom new to you know to get
empathy but about tonight
so now the question comes provide me a
koala many lifetimes are in one turning
of the twelve links come on you keep
some time off from wake up me angry
and why it's not just one lifetime like
Shakespeare what I shall contain the
McCook now you should be annoying to
find out the answer that came back to
July to come back to tomorrow's session
number 17 - wait July my phone name is
on somewhere bye see you there hang up
like Japan